We'll be right back.
Sanji barges in.
Sea train battle in the storm.
Ow! Seriously, what was that guy trying to pull anyway?
Whatever the case, it really doesn't matter.
That was a government train.
It'll be captured and that will be the end of it.
Hey, isn't he with Galila?
Hey, Paul!
Try to act professional, will ya?
It looks like there's something going on between them.
This is a train station.
People say hello and goodbye here every day.
It's our responsibility as employees here to silently oversee things like this.
Yeah, you're right.
Keep quiet, got it?
Quiet, got it.
Train left a little early, huh?
Uh, yes, that's right.
All of the passengers were already on board, so they decided...
The weather's getting rougher by the minute, too.
At this rate, Aqua Laguna could hit at any moment.
With all of these factors in mind, it was decided that departure time should be pushed forward.
It's not safe here right now.
You should take shelter on the shipbuilding island as soon as possible.
That goes for the young lady as well.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, listen.
The train's gone.
There's nothing we can do to stop it.
I hate to say it, but...
Annie's Lobby isn't the kind of place where...
Are you crying?
Hey, look, I...
I understand how you must feel, but...
After them!
She's passed!
I'll never forgive those world government idiots!
Listen, I need a ship!
What in the hell are you talking about?
The strongest and fastest you've got!
You want to set sail in the middle of all this?
Don't be an idiot!
Do you have any idea how dangerous this storm is?
Lay off!
I can handle it!
Look, this isn't some regular run-of-the-mill storm we're talking about!
It's about to be hell at sea around here!
It's impossible to sail out now!
Doing so is nothing short of a death wish!
Listen to me!
Robin is throwing her life away for our sake,
and I'm not gonna let...
Whoa!
Oh no!
That was close.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you!
You saved us all!
If it wasn't for you, we would have all been swept out into the sea.
Look at that.
That huge fixture with the train schedule on it was torn apart.
Nothing like that has ever happened here before.
Not even with Aqua Laguna.
This thing's power is unbelievable.
And the actual storm isn't even here yet.
Aqua Laguna is different this year.
These waves are coming in fast.
Hey, is that sea train that they took Robin on in any danger?
It should be able to make it out of this rough patch before the actual storm makes landfall.
Unless it takes a direct hit that train's capable of cutting through these big waves.
Um, excuse me, are you Nami?
Huh? Yes?
Someone left you a note out in front of the station.
Must have been one of your crewmates.
A note? From who?
And how did you manage to notice something so small?
It was right here. Whoever it was made it easy for us.
That dimwit.
So what does it say?
Give me a second.
The first half is just a hopeless love letter.
Did she say love letter?
It seems there's a love triangle going on here.
No. Considering the situation, I'd say the other man is most likely...
What are you staring at?
The important part starts here.
P.S. I saw Robin get on the 11 o'clock train.
I'm gonna hop on board and follow her.
P.S. Sanji got on board that train?
Usopp's there too?
And some arrogant thug with a duck tail.
Who's that?
That must be Frankie.
Yeah, must be.
She mentioned another man.
And it sounds like Frankie of all people must be the fifth.
Poor Polly doesn't stand a chance.
Maybe it'd be better if he just threw in the towel.
What in the hell is with you guys?
Oh, and there's something else.
This was left on the ground alongside that letter.
There should be at least one transponder snail somewhere on that C-train.
I'll contact you as soon as I can.
Keep this portable one close to you at all times, my darling.
Just pretend it's me and hold it lovingly against your soft...
I get it.
He left this one to communicate with us.
Wow, he must have anticipated Nico Robin's movements.
Pretty impressive.
I'll say.
At least for the time being, Robin has Sanji with her.
The rest of us will just have to catch up with them at Innie's lobby.
Man, can't even manage to light up a single smoke out here.
Really?
So after that, Sanji went to the train station?
Yep.
And Usopp's on the train with him.
Thank goodness.
At any rate, no matter how we're going to follow them,
we can't do anything until we find Luffy and Zoro first, understand?
Right.
I got it, Nami.
I'm a hundred percent certain about which way they flew,
so head in that direction and start looking.
You guys help look too!
Let's do this!
Are you with me?
Yeah!
We won't let you down!
Now, what would be the best way for one to sneak inside this thing?
Whoa!
This storm is insane!
Who in the hell are you?
Ah!
Hey, hold it!
Where do you think you're going?
Don't move!
Whoa!
Did you see that kick?
He's not some run-of-the-mill civilian.
Huh?
Come on, now.
If you keep saying things like that...
I'll blush.
It wasn't a compliment!
He's making fun of us.
Hey, go let Rob Lucci know that we've got a suspicious intruder on board.
Wait a minute!
Huh?
This insignificant little matter isn't something we need to bother CP9 with.
No matter how violent or unruly this man is,
it won't do him any good.
Because in this car, you've got...
Whoa!
It's smoke!
In this car, you've got me, Jerry!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
That's right.
You're looking at the champion on a South Blue Island renowned for its martial arts.
The undefeated boxing champion!
I prefer karate.
If you can handle my punches, then maybe I'll show you some.
Ah!
Easy!
No need to overdo it!
Jerry!
A-ra-ra!
The girl!
J-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j-j!
Hey, Jerry, your target's behind you.
You're a sneaky one.
Now listen, don't think you have me at a disadvantage
just because I'm so very tall and this train car is so very tiny.
This is the first time I've ever talked to someone
whose head is where their crotch should be.
My boxing technique is more effective in tight places like this.
Prepare for annihilation!
Go yoga style!
One, two!
You just shortened your reach!
That's what you think.
All part of the band!
BROCKY!
That's totally against every single rule of boxing!
This is a waste of time.
Oh, shit!
I'll start with the seventh and last car.
All of the world government officials are there.
In order of increasing strength, the fifth car is next.
That car holds 40 Marines and the man who leads them,
a Navy headquarters captain and former knight named T-Bone.
Next in the fourth car, we have Wanzai,
an accomplished martial artist from Cypherpole number seven,
who also happens to be the head steward on this trip.
Standing by in the third car is Nero,
the newest member of CP-9 and a force to be reckoned with.
Anyway, although we are escorting criminals with government personnel
as trained and powerful as the ones I mentioned,
we needn't worry about the possibility of a raid.
Our military might is represented throughout this train.
Straw help!
Nero!
We're here to help!
Come out!
Where are you?
Mr. Foreman, it must be hard for you to even move.
Maybe you should take a little break.
Don't be stupid. This is nothing.
Hurry up and find them.
Yes, sir.
Has anyone gone to bring Iceberg up to speed?
Two men went to give him a report.
Hey, where are you going, Mr. Iceberg?
Sir?
Hey, Zorro!
Where are you?
Answer us, Straw Hat!
Woofie!
Zorro, Woofie!
Come on, guys, answer me!
Where the heck are you?
What's that?
Food, you say?
Yes, that's right.
We need meat.
All the meat you can find.
And hurry, we're running out of time.
How did we end up being a couple of errand boys for that girl?
We're not doing this for her.
We're doing it for Pauly.
He's so devoted to that crazy woman,
even after she dumped him.
We've got to give this our all.
Yeah, you're right.
Keep going.
In any case, she must be really hungry.
She's still a growing girl, right?
I guess.
It's no use.
None of the stores are open.
Everyone's evacuated.
Hey, wait a minute.
What about the kitchen back at the train station?
No way.
Think about it.
The back streets are probably already flooded.
Then we've got no choice but to keep looking around here.
But...
Let's get moving.
What do you think will happen if we show up empty-handed?
Oh, rain.
This is bad.
The strong winds are already interfering with my sense of smell.
Oh, rain.
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋れる海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも勇敢で思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
次回予告
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!
Hey Nami! I kinda got stuck here when that leopard guy sent me flying
Listen! Robin was lying to us!
She was?
About what?
She's sacrificing herself in order to protect us!
Then let's get going! We gotta protect her!
On the next, One Piece! Nami's soul cries out! Straw Hat Luffy makes a comeback!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!